One dream, one wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top.
I better grab him and run.
I can do that much at least.
Room.
Sham.
Something set my power away.
You've caused enough trouble, Trafalgar.
Hawkins.
Huh, just what I need—sea prism
stone comes from this land;
it's only natural to Weapons it here.
A
sea prism stone—nail the artisans here
can craft it in such a small scale.
You must admire their expertise.
Draw a
sword.
Screw this
crap.
I can't get out of here. Now roam.
And sample.
That ability
of yours is a nuisance.
He won't
get very far.
Let's spread
out and search for him.
Quickly.
Yes, sir.
What the
boy up. Yes, sir.
His spirit will be broken in time.
Then he can join us. Yes, sir.
Don't mention a word about pirates
in the notice papers. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir
The people in this country don't know
a damn thing about the outside world,
and I want to keep it that way.
You understand me?
Yes, sir! Let's go! Come on!
Stop your gawking and grab his feet!
Right!
You have it too, pesky runt.
There's no way.
That technique, it was
the same as Lord Odin's.
But how can he use it when
he's knocked out cold?
Who the hell is he?
Where did he come from?
Fancy yourself a conqueror, do you?
There's too many already!
And none of them worth a damn!
I'll deal with Trafalgar later.
I'm going back to drinking.
I've sobered up after all that crap.
C-prism stone nails, huh?
That's gonna be a real pain in the ass.
All right, what's next?
Captain, help!
I hope my crew survive back there.
Excuse me, sir!
Have you tracked down
Trafalgar yet? No, sir.
We've been looking all over
town, but he's not here.
He must have made a break for it fast.
Go on. Cuff him. Yes, sir!
Capturing Straw Hat should be
sufficient for the time being, at least.
Just wait.
I will not be deterred.
Hide if you must, Trafalgar.
But I will find you.
It's Caribou!
Hey, hang in there, pal!
I'm going to treat you now, all right?
I'd know that voice anywhere.
Such a waste.
Luffy Taro.
He did so much for us.
And look what became of
all the food he brought.
I want to tell him how sorry I am.
Luffy Taro would never blame you for that.
Though I do worry that when he sees
the sorry state of things here,
he's going to blame himself.
That man has such a gentle heart.
Still as beautiful as a painting, you
haven't changed in 20 years. And yet,
I dare not show my face to you until I
have fulfilled the dream of our Lord Odin!
My darling, please forgive
your selfish husband!
It can't be.
That's Ashura Doji.
What is this hole?
Okiku!
No, it couldn't be.
Can you help us?
A giant sinkhole opened
up, as you can say.
Who can you save me?
Thankfully, we all made it out okay.
I'm so happy.
I feared the worst had happened.
The sinkhole saved us,
but there's one issue.
We saw him!
Oh, please, no!
Hold on tight, okay, ladies?
That was great, Sanji!
Such a strong boy!
My work is done.
The ladies are all safe.
Well, that was quite harrowing.
So when Kaido attacked the castle, Shino
protected everyone with her technique?
Precisely!
In that moment...
BLAST BREATH!
Right brave entitlement jutsu manifest!
Let's start, boys!
We did it!
We're alive!
My jutsu causes anything that I touch to
ripen suddenly or to become more mature.
One might say?
Indeed, everything that Chino
touches will spoil and rot away.
How rude now that we're safe?
Let me explain some things, oh yeah?
Do you know what happened to Luffy?
It seemed he was picking a fight
with Kaido, but that can't be right!
Prepare yourselves and listen!
Does his cruelty know no bounds?
Thank goodness, she's still breathing.
Then let us help her.
Yes, sir.
We might be spotted here; we should move.
What kind of monster would harm a child?
Curse you!
Kaido.
Lofitaro's battle in Kuri became big news.
Special report! Special report!
You're not going to want to miss this one.
ladies and gentlemen.
Soon the entire land of One-O was talking.
Huh?
You got some news?
Hey! It's Luffy!
Wonder how he's...
Doug!
Oh, it's Luffy.
So he made it.
Special reports.
There he is.
It burns!
To think that such a dangerous madman
was out roaming the streets. Yikes.
Madman did what now?
Oh, some samurai named Luffy Taro
had a fight with Commander Kaido.
If you don't like wasabi, don't eat it,
but I won't tolerate you
spitting on other customers.
How much did you eat?
Hold on, have you even paid?
Let me see that.
What the hell did you do, Luffy?
Beat that iron. Beat it flat.
Hard work makes strong weapons,
which means more business and
more riches for the capital.
Remember your life belongs to Lord Attack.
If you can't serve him,
we'll throw you away.
I'll kill you myself if I have to.
Hurry it up!
Udon in the land of Wano.
Home to a series of mines
and weapon factories.
Where prisoners are forced to slave away?
further lining the Shogun's pockets.
Hungry?
Here's your fish.
What the hell is in there anyway?
Creeps me out. Beats me.
All they said was stay back and
feed it a poisonous fish once a day,
but be sure to remove
the bones, freaky right?
Are you serious?
This thing likes poisonous fish.
Well, at first, the idea was to feed
it poisonous an execution method,
but it keeps eating the fish.
Not many people have seen what's in there,
but I hear it's been surviving
like that for quite a while now.
Is it like a crocodile or something?
And why do we have to
remove the bones from
the fish if they just want the thing dead?
Why bother, right?
Just trust me.
Heinous criminal, huh?
Must be that kid, the crazy one
that took on commander Kaido. Really
hope you
like your new home.
Doesn't look so tough?
You think we're...
I'm gonna let you live after
the stunt you pulled out there!
Welcome to hell!
Come on, let's hurry it up!
Damn, sure that's the right guy?
When I heard about all the
wild stuff he did in Carrot,
I kind of expected him to
be a little more impressive.
Crazy, huh?
Dude's tiny as hell.
Yeah, I thought he'd have a little more
presence, like the lead performers.
Hey, you gonna say something?
Why is he so weak? No surprise,
but Commander Kaido must have really
done a number on this little moron.
Hey, this isn't nap time. Get up!
Whoa, that's some luck.
It's all right.
Give us a couple days.
We'll beat that attitude right out of you.
I guarantee it.
Clearing at the guards on his first day.
He's asking for it.
That's it.
I'm teaching you a lesson.
How do you like this?
Aaaaaaah!
Grr!
A fishbone came flying out
of the cell! What idiot!
That's why you gotta
remove them first! Help!
I think I'm gonna die!
But damn!
What the hell could be in there anyway?
No one has a clue.
Say hello to your new home!
Unless you're ready to beg
Commander Kaido for mercy.
You're gonna be here a long time!
Starting bright and early!
We'll make you pay!
So sleep tight, sweetie.
I give that shrimp a week before
he's crying and pissing his pants!
Do you think the boss will
even want him after that?
Damn!
I'll get even with you, Kaido!
Oh, you!